<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on I AM COMPUTER_</title>
    <link>https://iamcomputer.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on I AM COMPUTER_</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://iamcomputer.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://iamcomputer.ca/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iamcomputer.ca/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are I AM COMPUTER_ — technical operators with over three decades of real-world experience across systems architecture, network engineering, IT support, design, and advanced hardware integration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We solve complex problems with speed, clarity, and precision — from building secure infrastructure to recovering critical systems and delivering custom-built solutions that others won’t touch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We value uptime, clean execution, and trust. When failure is not an option, we’re your failsafe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&#xA;operator.level: senior&#xA;protocols: systems | networks | design | hardware&#xA;status: always online&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;We fix what breaks. We build what doesn’t exist yet.&#xA;No noise. Just efficient, tailored results.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERMS</title>
      <link>https://iamcomputer.ca/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iamcomputer.ca/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Billing &amp;amp; Payment Terms&#xA;All services are billed in Canadian Dollars (CAD).&#xA;Invoices are payable via Interac e-Transfer or debit/credit card.&#xA;Alternate payment methods available upon request.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unless otherwise agreed in writing, all work is treated as confidential and may not be disclosed, published, or redistributed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Intellectual Property &amp;amp; Usage Rights&#xA;All deliverables remain the exclusive property of CMPTR INTL INC. until full payment is received.&#xA;Upon settlement, clients are granted the agreed usage rights — including source files and production assets, unless stated otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
